- Mr. Mills, how are you?.
- I'm fine.
- How are you?.
- Fine.
- I suppose you
wanna see it again?.
lf you don't mind.
- You know where it is.
- Oh, yeah.
If I charged you a
dollar every time...
you came to examine
the machine...
...you'd probably own it.
It's the one all the pros use.
Mariah Carey. Beyonce.
Gwen Stefani.
Really?. Who's Beyonce?.
Just kidding. I'll take it.
Excuse me, sir.
The adult party's
in the front.
- I'm Kim's father.
Excuse me, I work
for her father.
- Her real father.
- It's okay, Cyril. I got it.
- Hello, Bryan.
- Lenore.
I just wanted to give
Kim her present.
We're letting the kids
have their space.
- Put it with the others.
I wanna give it to her myself.
- Still having trouble
following the rules.
Oh, come on, Lennie.
- I've asked you not
to call me that.
Excuse me. Lenore.
- Dad.
- Oh, my darling.
- Hi.
- Hello, my sweet.
- Happy birthday.
- I was telling your father...
- ...how we arranged
the presents.
Here.
It's bad manners
to open the one...
- ...and not the others.
- Go on. Open it.
- Cool.
- A karaoke machine?.
- Well, I figured she
wants to be a singer.
When she was 1 2, Bryan.
- We've moved on.
- Thank you, Daddy.
My pleasure.
- I still wanna be a
singer. Don't tell Mom.
You got it.
Here. One for the book.
- We have a professional
photographer.
Big smile, sweetie.
That's my girl.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my-- Stuart.
Stuart, I love
you. I love you.
I love you.
Happy birthday, sweetie.
- Oh, Stuart,
you're impossible.
I know.
- Hey, Bryan.
- Stuart.
- She's not a little
girl anymore, huh?.
I guess not.
- Will you join us for lunch?.
- No, thanks.
I just wanted to be here
to wish her a happy birthday.
- Good to see you, Bryan.
- You too.
Thanks.
- Hey.
You forgot.
Come on in.
It's not like I didn't
call to remind you.
Third Saturday in May?.
- Red meat, red wine?.
Sound familiar?.
He probably had a
lot on his mind.
Yeah, the busy
life of a retiree.
Every day a new adventure.
What does a retiree
do, anyway?.
Take naps?. Play golf?.
- Hit on rich widows?.
That takes care
of the morning.
Yeah, well, come on, guys.
You know why I'm here.
Yeah, how's that going?.
Okay. We had her
birthday today.
Can you believe
my Kimmy's 1 7?.
Seventeen?.
- To Kim.
Lennie still got a
hard-on for you?.
She's not Lennie anymore.
She's Lenore.
Oh, she's still got a hard-on.
- And the husband?.
- The same. Perfect.
- Dig deep enough,
there's always shit.
We can dig if you
want us to dig.
What, you think he hasn't
done it already?.
Thank you, Bernie.
- How's Kimmy?.
- Good. She's good.
Yeah?. She sleep over yet?.
Well, let's say
we're working on it.
She appreciate the fact...
that you've given
up your life...
...in order to be
closer to her?.
What a life, huh?.
Hey, remember Beirut
after the chief disappeared?.
Bry was in deep with that
crazy sheik from Hezbollah?.
The guy said he'd
get us inside...
then disappeared.
We're scrambling to
get the hell out...
...before we get taken down
and where are you?.
I promised never to
miss her birthday.
Yeah, that went down well
at Langley...
...when they found out
you flew the coop...
...to attend your
child's birthday...
9000 miles away.
Where did you say
your next posting was?.
The Arctic Circle
spying on penguins.
I believe it was.
No, penguins live
in Antarctica.
Actually, it was Alaska.
What's your point, Sam?.
My point is we have
an open space.
Say the word, it's yours.
Who likes theirs rare?.
- Guys.
- See you, Bryan.
- Good night, guys.
- See you, Bry.
Hey, look, look, look.
All kidding aside...
...it's a great thing
trying to make up...
for lost time with Kimmy.
But tomorrow's
job?. Right here.
Four hours' work,
2500 bucks...
...just for taking
some pop diva...
to and from her concert.
- We're one short.
- A singer?.
I don't know if you'd
call her a singer.
More like a cash cow.
Twenty million records
sold already...
and she's not even 25.
Job's a piece of cake.
We get her there and back.
Inside, they've got
their own people.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay?.
- Yeah.
- Like that's it?.
Yeah.
- lt'll be perfect.
Just like old times.
Better. No one gets killed.
- Tomorrow. Good night, guys.
- See you.
- Get in the back, Wendy.
- I always get in the back.
Ma'am, if you don't mind,
I suggest you keep moving.
My mother is ma'am,
if you don't mind.
- Come on, it's time
now. Let's go.
Okay.
Bernie, Casey,
you're out here.
Bry, you're in the room.
Okay.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Thank you for coming.
Wow, it was beautiful.
Thanks. What did you say
your name was again?.
Mills. Bryan Mills.
- Nice to meet
you, Bryan Mills.
You too.
- You're on. Come
on, let's go now.
Okay, guys.
Excuse me, miss.
I've a daughter who
wants to be a singer...
and was wondering if
you had any tips.
Yeah, I do.
Tell her to pick
another career.
I got one.
We're waiting on
an air strike...
...and we're waiting...
and then my satellite
phone rings.
- Who is it?.
- Hello?.
- The guy we're to terminate.
- Honey.
- He'd like to know
if we want some tea.
Sorry, guys, it's Kim.
The noise?.
I'm at a concert.
You know this song?. Yeah?.
Yep, that's her.
No, no, no, I'm not attending.
I'm-- I'm not attending.
I'm helping some friends out
with security.
Well, of course I met her.
Who do you think's
guarding her?.
I'm glad you're impressed.
Hey, I'm happy you called.
I'm happy you called. What?.
Lunch?. Tomorrow?.
Sure, sure. I know the place.
Twelve-thirty it is.
I'll see you then.
- Here he is. And...?.
- What happened?.
- She wants to have lunch.
- Okay.
- Just the two of us.
- All right. Fantastic.
See?. There's
progress. That's great.
Who left that gate open?.
Bry, get her out of
here. Take the lead.
- Move.
- Go, go.
More security here now.
That's it. Move.
Casey.
Bernie, stand by, stand by.
- Go, go, go.
- Watch your head.
Here, take this.
The sugar will...
take the edge off the shock.
Come on, come on,
drink some more.
It's okay. It's
okay. You're safe.
You're safe now.
Bernie.
Casey. Rambo.
Seriously, Bry,
you should think
about coming with us.
You've got the edge.
There's more of
this to be had.
- She's going to
college next year?.
Yep.
- You're gonna lose her.
That gives me a
year to find her.
Mr. Mills, she'd
like to see you.
- How are you feeling?.
- Better.
So your daughter
wants to be a singer?.
Yep, since she was 5.
It's not what everyone
thinks it is.
Once the glam wears
off, it's just...
a lot of hotel rooms,
lots of airports.
It's what she wants.
The first number is Gio,
my vocal coach.
If he says she can
sing, she can sing.
He'll give her
coaching she needs,
the fee is on me.
The second number
is my manager.
If Gio clears her,
he'll make sure
she gets a shot.
- Thank you.
- No, Mr. Mills, thank you.
- There she is.
- Dad.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Don't look so excited.
I was just surprised.
I thought it was just
gonna be Kim and l.
I asked Mom to come.
One raspberry-banana
milkshake,
extra cherries, just
the way you like it.
- Thanks.
- Lennie-- Lenore.
- Would you like something?.
- I'm fine, thanks.
So?.
So, Dad, guess what.
- You know my friend Amanda?.
- Yep.
Her cousins asked us
to spend vacation...
with them in Paris.
How cool is that?.
- Why do you want
to go to Paris?.
Dad. Hello?.
The Louvre, the
lmpressionist museum,
the Picasso Museum.
I didn't know you
were so into art.
Are you kidding?. I've
been to the MOMA,
like, a hundred times.
Amanda went last
summer, she came...
back, she could
practically speak French.
And because you're
under 1 8...
...you need my permission
to leave the country?.
Dad, please. I really,
really wanna go.
They've got this...
sick apartment
overlooking the river.
- Just you and Amanda?.
- And her cousins.
Don't make a big deal
out of this, Bryan.
Just sign the paper.
- What?.
I'm not comfortable with this.
- Dad.
- I know the world, sweetie.
- Dad, please.
A 1 7-year-old should
not travel alone.
- I'm not gonna be alone.
- Two 1 7-year-olds.
Amanda's 1 9.
How about this?.
How about if I go along?.
You won't know I'm there.
I'm very good at
being invisible.
As you so amply demonstrated
for most of her life.
Just sign the paper, Bryan.
I'll think about it.
Everyone at this table
knows what that means.
Hey, Kimmy, there's
something else.
- I don't want anything else.
- Kim.
- I don't get you.
- What?.
You sacrificed our marriage
in the service of the country.
You made a mess of your life
in service of your country.
Can't you sacrifice a little
this time for your daughter?.
- I would sacrifice
anything for her.
What's your problem?.
I'm not comfortable
putting my daughter at risk.
Putting our daughter at risk
by going to Paris?.
You're pathetic.
- She's coming.
- Thanks.
Three conditions.
The address and phone number
of where you're staying.
You move, I wanna know where...
and with whom
you'll be staying.
Call me when you land. Call me...
every night before
you go to sleep.
It's international.
My number is in.
- Okay, awesome.
- Kimmy, you're not focused.
- I am.
- What did I say?.
You said call you when I land,
every night before
I go to sleep...
...your phone's international,
the number's programmed in.
Okay, one last thing.
I get to take you
to the airport.
Okay.
- There you go.
- Yes.
Thank you, Daddy.
Thank you, thank
you, thank you.
Mom.
I love you, Dad.
Mom, he signed
it, he signed it.
I'm gonna go call Amanda.
Wouldn't it have been easier
to sign the first time?.
Wouldn't it have been easier...
if you and I had talked
about it first?.
Certain areas in Paris
you should avoid.
I've written them down.
- Dad.
- Come on, take it.
We're gonna be
spending 90 percent...
of our time in
museums. Don't worry.
That's like telling water
not to be wet, sweetie.
Mom says
your job made you paranoid.
Well, my job made me aware.
I used to ask Mom
what your job was...
that you were away
all the time.
And she would tell
me to ask you.
Whenever I did see you,
I was afraid to ask.
Yeah?. Why?.
I don't know. Maybe because...
...I was afraid to find out.
Like, maybe it was something
I wouldn't like.
I worked for the government.
You knew that.
So you were like
a spy, right?.
- What happens if I
push this button?.
Don't touch that button.
Well, no, I was a--
I was a preventer, actually.
- A preventer?.
- Yeah.
What did you prevent?.
Bad things from happening.
So it was a good job?.
Yes. Yep, it was.
Do you miss it?.
I missed you more.
- Kim.
- Dad, there's Amanda.
Go ahead. I'll get the bags.
- Jimmy'll give you
a hand with those.
I can manage.
Lenore.
Do you know about this?.
She's not just going to Paris.
- I know.
- She lied to me.
Yes, because she
can't be honest...
with you.
Why?. What are you
talking about?.
Your rules and conditions.
What is this?.
It's U2's European tour dates.
She's following a rock band
around Europe?.
All kids do. Stuart
got her tickets,
arranged her to stay
in the best hotels.
Best hotels. You know,
you live in your
little bubble here...
...behind your wall,
with your maids...
and chauffeurs and servants.
No idea what the
world is like.
Yes, and neither will she...
unless she goes out
and experiences it.
Don't tell me I
don't know the world.
For five years I waited
for a phone call...
that didn't come
for weeks at a time.
For a knock on the door...
telling me there'd
be no calls anymore.
Listen, I know you
moved here to build...
some sort of
relationship with Kimmy.
But you're not gonna do that
by smothering her.
Let her live, or I promise,
I promise you'll lose her.
Girls.
Kim.
I love you.
Let's go. Come on.
I'll teach you
the French words
I know.
- Which may not be
that much, but--
Okay. Yeah, right.
Three. Okay, now take one--
Need some help?.
One with the two of you?.
Yes, please.
- Okay.
- He's really cute.
Okay. Yeah, great. Very nice.
Where are you from?.
California.
No. I'm Peter.
- This is Kim.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
Hey.
You're going into Paris?.
You know, taxis here
are so damned expensive.
Want to share?.
- Yeah. Sure.
- Okay, perfect.
Thanks.
To check arrivals,
please press one.
Please enter the
flight number.
Flight 288 arrived
in Paris Charles de Gaulle...
...at 8 a.m. Iocal time.
Yeah.
Oh, are you serious?.
- Oh, my God.
- Nice address.
Oh, yeah, thanks.
It' s my cousins',
but they're in Madrid,
so we have the whole
place to ourselves.
How cool is that?.
- I didn't know that.
- It's no biggie.
Well, I have to be going.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh, okay.
- You too.
- Bye.
Hey.
There is a party
tonight at school.
Want to come?.
- Sure. Yeah.
- We don't even know him.
What is there to
know?. He's hot.
- I come pick you up around 9?.
- Okay, yeah.
Okay, great. Your apartment?.
- It's the whole fifth
floor. Hoffmann.
Okay. See you tonight. Bye.
Bye.
Yeah.
Fifth floor.
Two girls around 1 8.
Oh, my God.
- How sick is this?.
Are you kidding
me?. It's great.
I just wish you
would've told me...
they weren't gonna be here.
- What's the difference?.
- I told my dad they'd be here.
You told your dad you were
going to museums too.
Oh, come on. He's
not gonna know.
- I'm gonna sleep with him.
- Who?.
- Peter.
- You just met him.
I hear French guys
are amazing in bed.
- Maybe he has a friend, huh?.
- No.
- Oh, come on.
You gotta lose it sometime.
Might as well be in Paris.
Hey.
- Amanda, where's
the bathroom?.
What?.
I have to pee.
- Hello?.
- It's me. Has Kim called you?.
Bryan, she's 1 7.
She's in Paris.
Give her some space.
She'll call. Take
a sleeping pill.
Have a drink or
something. Good night.
Good night.
Hi, Daddy.
Kim.
What did I say?.
You were supposed to call me.
I'm sorry.
I thought something was wrong
with the phone.
- No. It was such a
rush at the airport.
All right.
Well, if I'd had the number
where you were staying...
...I would've just
called there.
What's the number?
- I don 't have it.
- Kimmy, come on.
This is one of the conditions.
Let me talk to the cousins.
I'll get it from them.
Dad, they're in Spain.
I didn't know. I swear.
To Spain?.
Kim, is there anything else
you want to tell me?.
Kimmy.
- There's someone here.
- The cousins are back?.
No.
- Oh, my God. They got Amanda.
- What?.
What are you talking
about? Kimmy?
- Dad.
- Kim.
- Dad. They took her.
- They took her.
- All right, listen to me.
Oh, God.
- Did you meet anyone
on the plane?.
No.
- ln the airport?.
- No. Yes, Peter.
- Peter?. Peter who?.
- I don 't know.
- An American?.
- No.
Did he know where
you were staying?.
He took a cab with us.
Dad, they're coming.
- Please, I'm scared.
- I know you are.
Stay focused, Kimmy.
You have to hold it together.
How many people are there?.
- Three, four. I don't know.
- Where are you?.
- I'm in the bathroom.
- Go to the next bedroom.
Get under the bed.
Tell me when you're there.
- I'm here.
Now, the next part
is very important.
They are going to take you.
Kim, stay focused,
baby. This is key.
You will have five,
maybe ten seconds.
Very important seconds.
Leave the phone on the floor.
Concentrate.
Shout out everything
you see about them.
Hair color, eye color,
tall, short, scars.
Anything you see.
You understand?.
They're there.
I can hear them.
Remember, concentrate.
Put the phone closer
so I can hear.
They're leaving.
I think they're--
Beard. Six feet.
Tattoo right hand,
moon and star.
I don't know who you are.
I don't know what you want.
If you are looking
for a ransom.
I can tell you, I
don't have money.
But what I do have...
are a very particular
set of skills.
Skills I've acquired
over a very long career.
Skills that make
me a nightmare...
for people like you.
If you let my daughter go now,
that'll be the end of it.
I will not look for you.
I will not pursue you.
But if you don't, I
will look for you.
I will find you...
...and I will kill you.
Good luck.
Sam, it's me. I need a favor.
I'm gonna download something.
I need it analyzed. Right now.
- She's been taken.
- What?.
- Any enemies overseas?.
- Why would I have enemies?.
You do business overseas...
through multiple
shell corporations.
You were involved in
an oil deal with...
a bunch of Russians
that went south.
- How do you know that?.
I was not gonna
let my daughter...
...Iive with someone
without knowing...
everything about them.
- I have a few resources--
Now is not the time
for dick measuring.
- Anyone looking to hurt you?.
- Not that I know.
- Which room's Kim's?.
- What happened?.
I got a call from her.
There were people...
in the apartment.
She was taken.
- Oh, God.
- Which one?.
That one.
Is there something
I should be doing?.
You have a lease agreement...
with NetJet through
your company.
I do.
- Get me a plane to Paris.
- For when?.
An hour ago.
- I'm gonna make the
call. You all right?.
Yeah, yeah. I'm okay.
Would you please
get her back to me, Bryan?.
First I have to find her.
Sam, what have you got?.
They're speaking Albanian.
Based on their
accents and dialects,
they must be from Tropoja.
The place is ground zero
for scummers.
Even the Russians
give these guys a wide berth.
The one you spoke to,
his name is Marko.
We have information
that a mobster boss...
... by the name of Marko Hoxha...
moved to Paris about
six months ago.
If he's the one,
he's a big fish.
The tattoo, by the
way, is a group ID.
- Am I on speaker or
are you by yourself?
Lenore is here.
- Hey, Lennie.
- Hello, Sam.
She needs to hear it, Sam.
The specialty of the
groups coming out...
of this area is
trafficking in women.
- Keep going.
- Okay.
Their previous m.o.
was to offer women...
from emerging East
European countries...
...Iike Yugoslavia,
Romania, Bulgaria,
jobs in the West as
maids and nannies.
Once smuggled in,
they'd addict them...
to drugs and turn them
into prostitutes.
Lately, however,
they've decided...
that it's more economical...
...just to kidnap
traveling young women.
Saves on transportation costs.
Oh, my little baby.
What else?.
Based on the way
these groups operate,
our analyst says...
...you have a 96-hour window
from the time she was grabbed.
- To what?.
- To never finding her.
No, no, no.
Daddy.
Mustache. Six feet.
Tattoo on right
hand, moon and star.
Da--
Good luck.
Oh, my God.
Dad, they got Amanda.
Oh, God.
Dad, they got her.
They took her.
Go to the next bedroom.
Get under the bed.
- Tell me when you're there.
- I'm here.
Stay focused, baby.
Leave the phone on the floor.
Concentrate. Shout out
everything you see about them.
Hair color, eye color,
tall, short, scars.
Anything you see.
You understand?
They're there.
I can hear them.
Remember, concentrate.
They're leaving. Daddy.
Dad.
Beard. Six feet.
Tattoo right hand,
moon and star.
Dad.
- Hi.
- I ' m Peter.
- I ' m lngrid.
- On holidays?.
- Yes.
- Me too.
- Cool.
Cabs here are so
damned expensive.
Want to share?.
- Sure. Why not?.
- Great.
- Excuse me.
- Hey.
- Drive.
- The two American
girls from yesterday?.
I don't know.
The next rib drives
into your lungs.
The two American girls,
where are they?.
- Just like the old days.
Would you have it
any other way?.
Between you and me?. No.
But now that I
sit behind a desk,
the world looks different.
- You mean, looks boring.
- I mean different.
Okay, a little boring.
But is being retired...
any more interesting?.
It wasn't. Until my daughter...
disappeared in
Paris yesterday.
She and her friend
were marked by a...
spotter at the airport.
Albanians took her.
- How do you know this?.
- I'm retired, not dead.
And I assume you don't want
to go to the police.
I was told I have 96 hours.
That was 1 6 hours ago.
- Okay, first, we should
find the spotter.
I found him, he's dead.
You found him that way?.
Bryan, you cannot
just run around...
tearing down Paris--
I'll tear down the
Eiffel Tower...
if I have to.
- Don't forget who you talk to.
- I'm talking to a friend.
You are. But please remember,
your friend has a desk now.
'Deputy director,
lnternal Security.'
Very impressive.
The Albanians?.
They showed up from the East,
six, seven years ago.
Fifteen, 20 of them.
Now there are hundreds.
We don't even know how many.
And dangerous.
So I heard. Where
do I find them?.
The best place to start
is Porte de Clichy.
Bryan, try not to make a mess.
- Gregor Milocivic?.
- Yes. Yes, I am Gregor.
I'm Mr. Smith. Get in.
Here is my resume.
The employment agency said...
we would be doing
translations.
Yes. Albanian to English.
You do speak Albanian?.
Albanian, Serbian, Croatian.
I was a teacher in
primary school...
- ...before the war
began in Pristina--
What's your rate?.
My rate?.
It is 25 per hour for
the first three hours...
and then it goes up--
Okay. Now, here's
for 1 0 hours.
Wait here.
Mr. Smith, I do
not understand.
What is the job exactly?.
Right now the job
is to wait here.
Good evening.
- Hi. Looking for a date?.
I love your dress.
Is that silk?.
I don't know.
You want to know the prices?.
Just the way it falls,
it must be silk.
How it compliments...
the natural curves
of your body.
The rate is 40 euros
for the standard.
Standard?. Could you
be more specific?.
Back home, the standard covers
a range of possibilities.
Like kissing,
you know, closed
lips, open lips.
- lf you're not
buying, piss off.
I didn't say I wasn't buying.
I like to get comfortable
before I purchase.
Like this karaoke
machine I bought.
I must have read that manual...
from cover to cover
so many times.
I don't give a shit.
You're gonna...
get me in trouble
if you don't buy.
- Trouble?. Really?. With who?.
- Piss off.
Okay, okay. Listen, I'm sorry.
If I want a package deal,
do I get a discount?.
- You cost me two now.
- My name's Bryan.
- Oh, God. You better leave.
I thought we were negotiating.
Anton, I swear,
it's not my fault.
- I told him--
Why are you
bothering the girl?.
- None of your business.
- She is my business.
And if you're not
spending money,
you're costing money.
- I was negotiating.
No negotiating.
Price is the price.
Now you owe me
for two that got away.
I don't owe you nothing.
- Fifty euros or
I kick your ass.
Sure, sure, okay.
Chill.
Okay. Here's your 50.
And another 50 for
being an asshole.
Now get the hell out of here.
If I see you again,
I'll kill you.
Mr. Smith, I do not
know what kind of...
job I'm supposed to
do for you, but--...
- You are to translate.
- Yes. But translate what?.
This.
Translate.
- They're talking about you.
- What about me?.
- They're not saying
nice things.
Be specific.
They're saying--
Excuse me, Mr. Smith.
- what an asshole you are.
Please, if you can
explain to me...
why we're doing this--
Just translate.
One of them says,
the sausage gave
him heartburn.
Keep going.
The other one is
suggesting something...
his grandmother
used to give him.
- Do you really want
to hear all this?.
Every word.
Now they're talking
about football.
The game between
Lazio and Marseille.
And they lost money
on the betting.
- Perhaps if I knew
the purpose--
You're better off not knowing.
Is it still football?.
One is on the phone.
He has to do a job
at the construction site.
Something about
fresh merchandise...
giving problems.
Mr. Smith,
I do not understand
any of this.
You're not supposed
to. Goodbye.
I asked for an En
glish-Albanian...
dictionary, did
you bring one?.
Thank you.
I love you.
Where did you get this?.
- I'm good.
- Who gave this to you?.
- Who--?. Who gave
this to you?.
I'm good.
Hey.
Come on.
Monsieur Allen, how are you?.
Hello, Gilles.
How's the wife?.
Well, still in charge.
- Been a long time
since I've seen you.
Way too long.
- The usual accommodation?.
- Plus one.
Yes?.
- We need to talk.
- I'm listening.
Well, can't you come
and meet me first?.
I can't see you.
Where are you?.
I can see you and
hear you very well.
You can tell them
to stop jogging now.
Didn't think
I was gonna come
down, did you?.
I didn't think you were gonna
make such a mess.
I didn't have time to worry
about neatness.
- I know. You have 70 hours.
- Now I have 56.
No, now you have none.
My chief wanted to arrest you,
I convinced him
to send you home.
Air France 001
leaves today at 2.
First class.
Courtesy of the
French government...
for past services rendered.
- And what about my daughter?.
I told you, I sit
behind a desk now.
I take my orders from someone
who sits behind a bigger desk.
Come on, seven dead bodies,
three in hospital, a
building destroyed.
Total chaos at the airport.
He wanted your ass in chains.
It's the best I
could do, I'm sorry.
Sorry doesn't cut
it, Jean-Claude.
Not this time.
You can't beat
the state, Bryan.
You know that.
I'm not trying to.
I'm trying to
save my daughter.
It was a trailer,
not a building.
No, no, no. Leave it.
It's all right, it's fluids.
And medication
to counteract the drugs.
It's all right.
Where'd you get this?.
Where did you
get this jacket?.
Did you get it from her?.
Was it from this girl?.
I didn't steal it.
- I was cold, she
gave it to me.
Where?. Where did
she give it to you?.
- ln the house.
- What house?.
The house with the red door.
Sorry.
He said it was a party.
The girl who gave you this,
was she in the house?.
She was nice.
I know.
She's my daughter.
I need to find this house.
Do you know where it is?.
Paradise.
- Good morning.
- May I help you?.
- I'm here to see your boss.
- No boss.
We're doing
nothing wrong here.
One button,
and 30 agents will be here...
...before you have time
to scratch your balls.
Stop jerking around before
I close you down
for wasting my time.
Wait here.
You have weapon?.
You're holding it.
Black, one sugar, please.
What is it you want?.
I'm here to
negotiate the rates.
We already negotiated the rate
with Mr. Macon.
Mr. Macon has moved
to another division.
I'm here for the
renegotiation.
Unless you think I'm
being unreasonable,
let me explain ourselves.
Nice coffee. We have you under...
satellite surveillance,
24 hours a day.
We hear everything you say,
we know everything you do.
Do you have any idea
what it costs...
just to change the angle...
...of the lens on a satellite...
orbiting 200 miles
above the Earth?.
And those costs have gone up.
Our costs go up,
your costs go up.
It's only logical.
By the way,
which one of you is Marko?.
Why do you want to know?.
I was told Marko is in charge.
We are all Marko.
Marko from Tropoja.
We are all from Tropoja.
If that's the game
you want to play,
the rate just went
up 1 0 percent.
If you are trying to
extort us because...
we are immigrants,
we know the law.
I'm extorting you because
you are breaking the law.
Which charge would you
like to be arrested for?.
Drugs, kidnapping,
prostitution?.
Take your pick.
You come to this country,
take advantage of it...
...and think because
we are tolerant,
we are weak and helpless.
Your arrogance offends me.
For that,
the rate went up 1 0 percent.
Now, do you want to get down...
to business or to
keep playing?.
- How much?.
- Twenty percent.
And you have my word
it'll not go up...
for a year.
How do you say 'sugar'
in your language?.
You've made a very
good investment,
gentlemen.
See you in a month.
A friend gave this to me.
It's Albanian. You
mind translating it?.
Good luck.
- Good luck.
- Good luck. Good luck.
You don't remember me.
We spoke on the phone
two days ago.
I told you I would find you.
Kim.
Amanda.
Wake up.
I need you to be focused.
Are you focused yet?.
Where is this girl?.
Where is she?.
You know, we used to outsource
this kind of thing.
But what we found
was the countries...
we outsourced to...
...had unreliable power grids.
Very Third World.
You'd turn on a switch,
power wouldn't come on...
...and then tempers
would get short.
People would resort to
pulling fingernails.
Acid drips on bare skin.
The whole exercise...
would become co
unterproductive.
But here, the power's stable.
Here, there's a
nice even flow.
Here, you can flip a switch...
and the power
stays on all day.
Where is she?.
Now, I don't have
any more time...
to waste, Marko from Tropoja.
Give me what I need
or this switch'll stay on...
...till they turn power off...
for lack of payment
on the bill.
Where is my daughter?.
We don't keep virgins,
we sell them.
She was virgin, lot of money.
You sold my daughter?.
You sold her?.
To who?.
I don't know.
- What?.
- Saint-Clair.
Saint-Clair.
Saint-Clair?. Saint-Clair.
Is that a person, a place?.
Person. Patrice Saint-Clair.
Patrice Saint-Clair.
Where can I find him?.
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
Please. I don't know.
I don't know. No.
Please. Please.
Please.
Not that. Please.
I believe you.
But it's not gonna save you.
Look who dropped by.
Bryan, what a
pleasant surprise.
Jean-Claude.
The children
waited up for you.
If you tuck them in,
maybe we can eat...
before everything gets cold.
Bryan, will you
do the honors?.
- Sure.
- I'll be just a minute.
I was just telling Bryan
how nice it's been...
...since you left the old job
for the new one.
Home every night for dinner,
get to see the kids more.
Yeah, must be nice coming home
every night, seeing your kids.
Bryan has been thinking
about relocating.
- Really?.
- Yes.
To Paris, he's been
visiting houses.
- White or dark meat?.
- Dark, please.
Find anything interesting?.
As a matter of fact,
I did, in the 1 0th...
arrondissement on Rue Paradis.
People there know someone
that works in your office.
A Mr. Macon. Do you know him?.
Oh, Henry. I call
him Mr. Nervous.
Always seems like
he's about to...
have a problem. Carrots?.
I got to the bottom of it,
Jean-Claude.
I know everything.
I hope you're not
involved in this shit.
- What shit?.
This is not the time
or place, Bryan.
- Are you involved?.
- lnvolved in what?.
What are you two
talking about?.
- Are you?.
My salary is X, my
expenses are Y.
As long as my family
is provided for...
...I do not care...
where the difference
comes from.
That is my entire involvement.
- What about my family?.
- I told you...
...I would help...
as long as it didn't
cause trouble.
Who is Patrice Saint-Clair?.
I don't know, I don't care.
I am driving you
to the airport.
Jean-Claude.
Let's get going.
Dinner is over.
- I'm not finished yet.
- Yes, you are.
- No.
- No, I'm not.
That's what happens
when you sit...
behind a desk.
You forget things.
Like the weight in the hand
of a gun that's loaded.
Isabelle.
It's a flesh wound.
But if you don't
get me what I need,
the last thing you'll see...
...is the bullet
I put between her eyes.
Now, Patrice Saint-Clair.
You could've made this
less painful...
...if you had been more
concerned about...
my daughter and less
about your desk.
Please apologize to
your wife for me.
- Can I help you?.
Yes, I'm here to
see Mr. Saint-Clair.
Your name, please.
I'm sorry,
your name is not on the list.
Oh, please check again.
Inside.
May I help you, sir?.
- Your champagne.
- Yeah, I will take it.
I have 50,000. Fifty thousand.
Fifty thousand.
One hundred, 1 00,000.
One hundred, 1 50.
I have 1 50.
Your champagne, sir.
Two, I have two, 250.
May I serve?.
- Please.
- I have 250.
Two-fifty.
Sold for 250, 000.
The last item.
As usual, we save
the best for last.
Speaks English, some French.
Certified pure.
- Sorry.
- Get out.
The bidding will
begin at 1 00,000.
One hundred.
One hundred thousand.
- I said--
- I heard what you said.
Buy her.
I have 1 00.
- Buy her.
- One-fifty.
Two hundred.
Two-fifty, three, 350.
Three hundred and
fifty thousand.
Four. Four.
Four-fifty, 450.
Four hundred and
fifty thousand.
Four-fifty.
Five hundred. Five
hundred thousand.
Five hundred thousand. Sold.
That concludes the
sales for tonight.
Thank you all for coming.
- You can collect your
purchases directly.
Move.
- You will never
get away with this.
lf you wanna live, you
' ll make sure I do.
Now, Mr...?.
Well, we know you're
not this man.
So, what do we call you?.
It doesn't matter
what we call you...
...what does matter
is what you're doing here.
The last girl, I'm her father.
- Oh, my.
- Give her to me.
I wish I could, honestly.
See, I'm a father myself.
I have two sons
and a daughter...
...but let me tell
you something.
Mr. Whoever-You-Are.
This is a business.
This is a very
unique business...
- ...with a very
unique clientele.
I'll pay.
In this business,
you have no
refunds, returns...
...discounts, buybacks.
All sales are final.
Besides discretion,
it's about the
only rule we have.
Kill him. Quietly.
I have guests.
Would you please go see
which part of 'quietly'...
- ...they did not understand?.
- Yes, sir.
Okay, we can resolve this.
I know how you feel.
We should talk, okay?.
We can work this out.
You have no idea--...
- Where is she?.
- Please.
Understand. Please try--
There's a boat by the quay.
Please understand.
It was all business,
it wasn't personal.
It was all personal to me.
We can--...
- Daddy.
- Kim.
You came for me.
I told you I would.
May I have your attention.
If you're waiting
for oversized bags--
Mom.
Oh, my God.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, here, let me
get that for you.
Bryan, if there's
anything you need....
I've got everything I need.
I love you so much.
Stuart.
Thank you.
Attention, travelers.
You are not required to--
Shall we go?.
Sure you don't
wanna ride with us?.
- I'll be fine. I'll
take a cab. Thanks.
All right.
- I love you, Dad.
- Love you too.
- Where are we?.
- I told you. It's a surprise.
- Hi.
When someone says 'hi,'...
it's usually polite
to say 'hi' back.
Hi.
I heard you wanna be a singer.
- I do.
- She does.
Well, come on in.
Let's see what you got.